<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitHub on Contents</title>
    <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/github/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in GitHub on Contents</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Basics</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/github/basics/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/github/basics/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following GitHub skills and techniques may be considered basic level.
Basic GitHub [ ] Creating and cloning repositories: Know how to create new repositories on GitHub and how to clone existing repositories to your local machine so that you can work on them.
[ ] Adding and committing changes: Know how to add changes to your local repository and commit them so that they are saved to your repository&amp;rsquo;s history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/github/intermediate/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/github/intermediate/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following GitHub skills and techniques may be considered intermediate level.
Intermediate GitHub [ ] Working with branches: Know how to create and switch between branches, and how to merge changes between branches.
[ ] Using issues and pull requests: Know how to create and manage issues and pull requests, which are useful for tracking tasks, discussing changes, and requesting code reviews.
[ ] Collaboration: Know how to work collaboratively with others on a project using Git, including resolving merge conflicts and managing team workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/github/advanced/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/github/advanced/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following GitHub skills and techniques may be considered advanced level.
Advanced GitHub [ ] Git hooks: Know how to write and use Git hooks to automate tasks and enforce standards.
[ ] Git workflows: Know how to use Git workflows like GitFlow or GitHub Flow to manage complex projects and team collaboration.
[ ] Advanced Git commands: Be familiar with advanced Git commands like git cherry-pick, git bisect, and git stash.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>