<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows on Contents</title>
    <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/windows/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows on Contents</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Commnd Prompt</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/windows/command-prompt/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/windows/command-prompt/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Command Prompt is a basic terminal emulator that has been included in Windows since the early days. It provides a command-line interface for interacting with the file system, running basic commands, and executing batch scripts.
The Command Prompt supports a range of commands, including:
dir: List the contents of a directory. cd: Change the current directory. md: Create a new directory. del: Delete files. copy: Copy files. move: Move files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Bash</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/windows/git-bash/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/windows/git-bash/index.html</guid>
      <description>Git Bash is a terminal emulator that is bundled with Git for Windows. It provides a Unix-like command-line environment for Windows, including support for common Unix utilities and shell scripting. Git Bash includes a range of features and commands that are useful for developers working with Git repositories, including:
git: A command-line interface for interacting with Git repositories, including tasks like cloning, committing, pushing, and merging changes. ssh: A command-line interface for managing secure shell connections to remote servers and devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/windows/powershell/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/windows/powershell/index.html</guid>
      <description>PowerShell is a command-line shell and scripting language designed for system administration and automation in Windows. PowerShell provides a more powerful and flexible command-line environment than the Command Prompt, with support for features like object-oriented pipelines, remote management, and scripting with .NET objects.
PowerShell includes a wide range of built-in commands, called cmdlets, that provide access to various Windows management features, such as:
Get-Process: Display information about running processes, including process ID (PID), CPU and memory usage, and parent process ID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL)</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/windows/wsl/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/windows/wsl/index.html</guid>
      <description>Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) is a feature of Windows 10 that allows users to run a Linux environment directly on Windows, without the need for a virtual machine or container. WSL provides access to a full-fledged Linux system, including a terminal emulator and support for running Linux applications and scripts.
WSL supports two different versions:
WSL 1: Uses a translation layer to provide compatibility between Linux system calls and Windows kernel system calls.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>