<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contents</title>
    <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content on Contents</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Languages</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/languages/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/languages/index.html</guid>
      <description>This page provides an introduction for popular languages - some are programming languages - and some are markup languages.
CSS CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) is a stylesheet language used for describing the look and formatting of a document written in HTML. While not directly related to data analytics, it&amp;rsquo;s essential for creating visually appealing dashboards and reports.
Go (Golang) Go is a statically typed, compiled language with strong support for concurrent programming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/tools/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/tools/index.html</guid>
      <description>This section includes documentation for some of the tools we use.
Git Git is a popular version control system that allows developers to track changes to their code and collaborate with others on a project. It provides a way to manage and organize code, and allows for easy branching and merging. Git is widely used in software development, and is an essential tool for any developer&amp;rsquo;s toolkit.
GitHub GitHub is a web-based platform that provides a range of features for managing Git repositories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminals</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/terminals/index.html</guid>
      <description>A terminal, or command line interface, is a text-based way to interact with your computer. Terminals can be faster and more powerful than graphical user interfaces (GUIs) for many tasks, especially tasks that involve file management, development, or automation.
This page provides an introduction to some widely-used terminals.
Mac and Linux Mac and Linux systems offer the Terminal app, which provides a command-line interface for navigating the file system, running commands, and executing scripts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techniques</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/index.html</guid>
      <description>This page provides documentation and tutorials on various techniques used in data analytics and development.
Data Cleaning Introduction to Data Cleaning Data Visualization Introduction to Data Visualization Matplotlib Seaborn Machine Learning Introduction to Machine Learning Scikit-Learn TensorFlow Keras </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosting</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/hosting/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/hosting/index.html</guid>
      <description>This page provides an introduction to popular hosting providers.
BitBucket BitBucket is a popular hosting provider for Git repositories.
DockerHub DockerHub is a cloud-based repository for Docker images and containers.
GitHub GitHub is a widely used platform for hosting Git repositories, collaborating on code, and managing projects.
GitHub Pages GitHub Pages is a free service for hosting static websites directly from a GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/other/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/other/index.html</guid>
      <description>Few more things to share.
About Learn more about this site and the tools we used.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>