<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Git on Contents</title>
    <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/git/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Git on Contents</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/git/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Basics</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/git/basics/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/git/basics/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following Git skills and techniques may be considered basic level.
Basic Git Creating and cloning repositories: Know how to create new repositories on Git and how to clone existing repositories to your local machine so that you can work on them.
Adding and committing changes: Know how to add changes to your local repository and commit them so that they are saved to your repository&amp;rsquo;s history.
Pushing and pulling changes: Know how to push your local changes to your Git repository so that others can see them, and how to pull changes from the remote repository to your local machine to get the latest changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/git/intermediate/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/git/intermediate/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following GitHub skills and techniques may be considered intermediate level.
Intermediate Git Resolving merge conflicts: Learn how to handle conflicts that arise when merging branches or changes from multiple contributors.
Creating and managing branches: Know how to create and switch between branches, and how to merge changes between branches.
Using Git tags: Learn how to use Git tags to mark important points in your repository&amp;rsquo;s history, such as release versions or major milestones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced</title>
      <link>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/git/advanced/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://datafun-central.github.io/datafun-central/techniques/git/advanced/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following Git skills and techniques may be considered advanced level.
Advanced Git Rebasing: Know how to rebase a branch to update it with changes from another branch, while maintaining a clean history.
Cherry-picking: Know how to apply specific changes from one branch to another, without merging the entire branch.
Squashing commits: Know how to combine multiple commits into a single commit, to create a more coherent commit history.
Stashing: Know how to temporarily save changes that are not yet ready to be committed, so that you can work on other tasks without losing your progress.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>